Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President Records UA002
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1946 -- 2013; 1983 -- 1994; UA002.002; 33.6 Linear Feet; 1 Web sites
  - University-wide steering committee, 1972 -- 1973; UA002.002.019.00031 (Box 19)
  - University-wide steering committee, 1971 -- 1972; UA002.002.019.00032 (Box 19)
  - Upward Bound project, 1967 -- 1968; UA002.002.019.00033 (Box 19)
  - Upward Bound project, 1967 -- 1968; UA002.002.019.00034 (Box 19)
  - Upward Bound project, 1966; UA002.002.020.00001 (Box 20)
  - Upward Bound project, 1966 -- 1967; UA002.002.020.00002 (Box 20)
  - Urban and environmental policy, 1983 -- 1986; UA002.002.020.00003 (Box 20)
  - Urban studies planning, 1969; UA002.002.020.00004 (Box 20)
  - Veterinary school: correspondence, 1976; UA002.002.020.00005 (Box 20)
  - Veterinary school, 1976; UA002.002.020.00006 (Box 20)
  - Veterinary school, 1977; UA002.002.020.00007 (Box 20)
  - Veterinary school, 1977; UA002.002.020.00008 (Box 20)
  - Veterinary school: history, 1978; UA002.002.021.00001 (Box 21)
  - Veterinary school: history, 1979; UA002.002.021.00002 (Box 21)
  - Veterinary school: history, 1979; UA002.002.021.00003 (Box 21)
  - Visiting committee on personnel policy, 1976; UA002.002.021.00004 (Box 21)
  - Wells: special assistant to President, 1975 -- 1980; UA002.002.021.00005 (Box 21)
  - Westheimer, Dr. Ruth, 1984; UA002.002.021.00006 (Box 21)
  - Winter study, 1970 -- 1974; UA002.002.021.00007 (Box 21)
  - Ace fellow, 1978-79, Branca, Geraldine, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.002.049.00001 (Box 49)
  - ACNE colleges, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.002.049.00002 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences: Academic calendars, 1946 -- 1999; UA002.002.049.00003 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences block schedule: History, 1967 -- 1968; UA002.002.049.00004 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences faculty: College of Special Studies, 1954 -- 1988; UA002.002.049.00005 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences faculty: Crane School, 1953 -- 1968; UA002.002.049.00006 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences faculty: Engineering, 1953 -- 1990; UA002.002.049.00007 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences faculty: Graduate School, 1951 -- 1980; UA002.002.049.00008 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences faculty: Liberal Arts and Jackson, 1954 -- 1987; UA002.002.049.00009 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences faculty lists, 1 of 3, 1979 -- 1997; UA002.002.049.00010 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences faculty lists, 2 of 3, 1968 -- 1979; UA002.002.049.00011 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences faculty lists, 3 of 3, 1955 -- 1967; UA002.002.049.00012 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences faculty: Resolutions, 1959 -- 1984; UA002.002.049.00013 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences faculty: School of Nutrition, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.002.049.00014 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences faculty: School of Occupational Therapy, 1985 -- 1987; UA002.002.049.00015 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences reading and consultation period, 1963 -- 1967; UA002.002.049.00016 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences: Standing committees 1 of 4, 1988 -- 1997; UA002.002.049.00017 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences: Standing committees 2 of 4, 1976 -- 1988; UA002.002.049.00018 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences: Standing committees 3 of 4, 1963 -- 1976; UA002.002.049.00019 (Box 49)
  - Arts and sciences: Standing committees 4 of 4, 1953 -- 1963; UA002.002.049.00020 (Box 49)
  - Athletics committee, 1970 -- 1993; UA002.002.049.00021 (Box 49)
  - Boston technical high school, 1973 -- 1985; UA002.002.049.00022 (Box 49)
  - Budgets, 1979 -- 1980; UA002.002.049.00023 (Box 49)
  - Center of environmental management at Tufts, 1983 -- 1987; UA002.002.049.00024 (Box 49)
  - Center for plant conservation, 1984; UA002.002.049.00025 (Box 49)
  - Chemistry department: Problems and resolutions, 1970 -- 1981; UA002.002.049.00026 (Box 49)
  - Child study, Eliot-Pearson, 1964 -- 1981; UA002.002.049.00027 (Box 49)
  - Coal research consortium, 1976 -- 1981; UA002.002.050.00001 (Box 50)
  - College and university environment (CUES) scale, 1965 -- 1976; UA002.002.050.00002 (Box 50)
  - College writing requirements (sub-com-of LA and J), 1983 -- 1987; UA002.002.050.00003 (Box 50)
  - Commonwealth fund grant prop/biology, 1978 -- 1980; UA002.002.050.00004 (Box 50)
  - Commonwealth print conservation/Tufts, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.002.050.00005 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence, 1972 -- 1976; UA002.002.050.00006 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence-arts and sciences, 1983 -- 1984; UA002.002.050.00007 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence-dental school, 1979 -- 1984; UA002.002.050.00008 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence-engineering college, 1970 -- 1982; UA002.002.050.00009 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence-fine arts dept, 1966 -- 1981; UA002.002.050.00010 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence-Fletcher school, 1978 -- 1986; UA002.002.050.00011 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence-graduate school of arts and sciences, 1 of 2, 1978 -- 1989; UA002.002.050.00012 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence-graduate school of arts and sciences, 2 of 2, 1980 -- 1983; UA002.002.050.00013 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence-liberal arts/Jackson College, 1977 -- 1979; UA002.002.050.00014 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence-medical school, 1 of 3, 1980 -- 1988; UA002.002.050.00015 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence-medical school, 2 of 3, 1980 -- 1988; UA002.002.050.00016 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence-medical school, 3 of 3, 1980 -- 1988; UA002.002.050.00017 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence-nutrition school, 1980 -- 1983; UA002.002.050.00018 (Box 50)
  - Dean of student affairs, 1965 -- 1968; UA002.002.050.00019 (Box 50)
  - deBurlo (Treasurer), 1982 -- 1985; UA002.002.050.00020 (Box 50)
  - Decision making, 1978 -- 1989; UA002.002.050.00021 (Box 50)
  - Development, 1982; UA002.002.050.00022 (Box 50)
  - Development, 1 of 2, 1983; UA002.002.050.00023 (Box 50)
  - Development, 2 of 2, 1983; UA002.002.050.00024 (Box 50)
  - Development, 1984; UA002.002.050.00025 (Box 50)
  - Development, 1 of 2, 1985 -- 1988; UA002.002.051.00001 (Box 51)
  - Development, 2 of 2, 1985 -- 1988; UA002.002.051.00002 (Box 51)
  - Distribution requirements (L.A.), 1982 -- 1988; UA002.002.051.00003 (Box 51)
  - Engineering com. (academic standing), 1986 -- 1987; UA002.002.051.00004 (Box 51)
  - Engineering school committee, 1981 -- 1983; UA002.002.051.00005 (Box 51)
  - European center-Tallovies, 1 of 2, 1978 -- 1986; UA002.002.051.00006 (Box 51)
  - European center- Tallovies, 2 of 2, 1978 -- 1986; UA002.002.051.00007 (Box 51)
  - Facilities planning, 1976 -- 1982; UA002.002.051.00008 (Box 51)
  - Faculty club, 1968 -- 1989; UA002.002.051.00009 (Box 51)
  - Faculty development, 1977 -- 1985; UA002.002.051.00010 (Box 51)
  - Gerontology, 1977 -- 1989; UA002.002.051.00011 (Box 51)
  - Goals, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.002.051.00012 (Box 51)
  - Government resources, 1981 -- 1985; UA002.002.051.00013 (Box 51)
  - Grades, 1977 -- 1991; UA002.002.051.00014 (Box 51)
  - Graduate studies committee, 1985 -- 1987; UA002.002.051.00015 (Box 51)
  - Guest housing, 1982 -- 1987; UA002.002.051.00016 (Box 51)
  - Guidelines for full-time faculty appointments at Tufts University, 1987; UA002.002.051.00017 (Box 51)
  - Health facilities, 1983; UA002.002.051.00018 (Box 51)
  - Human nutrition research center (HNRC), 1982 -- 1989; UA002.002.051.00019 (Box 51)
  - Insurance, 1981 -- 1983; UA002.002.051.00020 (Box 51)
  - International health affairs com., 1988 -- 1989; UA002.002.051.00021 (Box 51)
  - Labor dept (wage), 1967 -- 1980; UA002.002.051.00022 (Box 51)
  - Liaison comm, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.002.051.00023 (Box 51)
  - Library, 1982; UA002.002.051.00024 (Box 51)
  - Library, 1981 -- 1989; UA002.002.051.00025 (Box 51)
  - Membership-university wide, 1978 -- 1993; UA002.002.051.00026 (Box 51)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981 -- 1987; UA002.002.051.00027 (Box 51)
  - Oceanic institute, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.002.051.00028 (Box 51)
  - Patent committee, 1979 -- 1983; UA002.002.052.00001 (Box 52)
  - Plans of study (LA and J), 1970 -- 1988; UA002.002.052.00002 (Box 52)
  - Pre-law, 1975 -- 1989; UA002.002.052.00003 (Box 52)
  - PIRG, 1981; UA002.002.052.00004 (Box 52)
  - Public health, 1981 -- 1983; UA002.002.052.00005 (Box 52)
  - Public service school (Tufts), 1987; UA002.002.052.00006 (Box 52)
  - Residences, 1981 -- 1983; UA002.002.052.00007 (Box 52)
  - Scheduling and registration committee, 1970 -- 1986; UA002.002.052.00008 (Box 52)
  - SDI (Star Wars), 1985 -- 1986; UA002.002.052.00009 (Box 52)
  - Security police (1980s security clearances), 1980 -- 1982; UA002.002.052.00010 (Box 52)
  - Statement on government of college and universities, 1967; UA002.002.052.00011 (Box 52)
  - Tax appeal, 1970 -- 1980; UA002.002.052.00012 (Box 52)
  - Taxes, 1969 -- 1982; UA002.002.052.00013 (Box 52)
  - Trustees-New England Medical Center (NEMC), 1979 -- 1983; UA002.002.052.00014 (Box 52)
  - Tufts-China executive development plan, 1 of 2, 1985 -- 1987; UA002.002.052.00015 (Box 52)
  - Tufts-China executive development plan, 2 of 2, 1985 -- 1987; UA002.002.052.00016 (Box 52)
  - Tufts disaster planning, 1970; UA002.002.052.00017 (Box 52)
  - Undergraduate admissions and financial aid (A&S), 1968 -- 1985; UA002.002.052.00018 (Box 52)
  - Undergraduate advising and counseling committee, 1972 -- 1988; UA002.002.052.00019 (Box 52)
  - Vista, 1969 -- 1970; UA002.002.052.00020 (Box 52)
  - World Trade Center, 1986; UA002.002.052.00021 (Box 52)
  - Audrey Hale file, 1968 -- 2009; UA002.002.052.00022 (Box 52)
    Materials compiled by Associate Provost Audrey Hale, many related to Provost Sol Gittleman.
  - Lincoln Filene Center [1 of 2], 1979 -- 1999; UA002.002.055.00001 (Box 55)
  - Lincoln Filene Center [2 of 2], 1979 -- 1999; UA002.002.055.00002 (Box 55)
  - Lincoln Filene correspondence, 1967 -- 1976; UA002.002.055.00003 (Box 55)
  - Memo of Understanding LFC Tufts, 1975 -- 1988; UA002.002.055.00004 (Box 55)
  - Executive Committee of Civic Education Foundation LFC [1 of 3], 1975 -- 1978; UA002.002.055.00005 (Box 55)
  - Executive Committee of Civic Education Foundation LFC [2 of 3], 1975 -- 1978; UA002.002.055.00006 (Box 55)
  - Executive Committee of Civic Education Foundation LFC [3 of 3], 1975 -- 1978; UA002.002.055.00007 (Box 55)
  - Lincoln Filene Center for Citizenship and Public History [1 of 2], 1961 -- 2000; UA002.002.055.00008 (Box 55)
  - Lincoln Filene Center for Citizenship and Public History [2 of 2], 1953 -- 1969; UA002.002.055.00009 (Box 55)
  - Summaries and reports Lincoln Filene Center, 1971 -- 1978; UA002.002.055.00010 (Box 55)
  - Lincoln Filene meetings [1 of 2], 1966 -- 1974; UA002.002.055.00011 (Box 55)
  - Lincoln Filene meetings [2 of 2], 1953 -- 1966; UA002.002.055.00012 (Box 55)
  - Civic Foundation Education LFC [1 of 2], 1975 -- 1977; UA002.002.055.00013 (Box 55)
  - Civic Foundation Education LFC [2 of 2], 1968 -- 1974; UA002.002.055.00014 (Box 55)
  - Lincoln Filene correspondence [1 of 2], 1963 -- 1973; UA002.002.055.00015 (Box 55)
  - Lincoln Filene correspondence [2 of 2], 1961 -- 1963; UA002.002.055.00016 (Box 55)
  - Tufts Assembly on Massachusetts Government [1 of 2], 1963 -- 1970; UA002.002.055.00017 (Box 55)
  - Tufts Assembly on Massachusetts Government [2 of 2], 1959 -- 1962; UA002.002.055.00018 (Box 55)
  - Accrediting- Gen., 1997 -- 2004; UA002.002.061.00001 (Box 61)
  - Accrediting Veterinary School, 2005; UA002.002.061.00002 (Box 61)
  - Accrediting- BSOT, 1979 -- 1997; UA002.002.061.00003 (Box 61)
  - Accrediting- Dental, 1987 -- 1997; UA002.002.061.00004 (Box 61)
  - Engineering Accreditiation, 2008 -- 2011; UA002.002.061.00005 (Box 61)
  - Accrediting- Medical, 1989 -- 1999; UA002.002.061.00006 (Box 61)
  - Consirtium, 2010; UA002.002.061.00007 (Box 61)
  - Academic Freedom, Tenure, & Retirement 2000-2010, UA002.002.061.00008 (Box 61)
  - Academic Affairs, 2009; UA002.002.061.00009 (Box 61)
  - Aidekman Arts Center, 2006 -- 2010; UA002.002.061.00010 (Box 61)
  - Chaplain, 1974 -- 2008; UA002.002.061.00011 (Box 61)
  - Coolidge Room, 2003; UA002.002.061.00012 (Box 61)
  - Crisis Management, 2000 -- 2010; UA002.002.061.00013 (Box 61)
  - Award Fellowship Applications, 2003 -- 2009; UA002.002.061.00014 (Box 61)
  - Foundations, 2002 -- 2004; UA002.002.061.00015 (Box 61)
  - Alumni Relations, 2007; UA002.002.061.00016 (Box 61)
  - Finance Division (McGurty), 2003 -- 2007; UA002.002.061.00017 (Box 61)
  - Tufts Development Corporation, 2006; UA002.002.061.00018 (Box 61)
  - Public Relations, 1987 -- 1997; UA002.002.061.00019 (Box 61)
  - Medford/Somerville, 1987 -- 2001; UA002.002.061.00020 (Box 61)
  - Human Resources 2001-, 2001 -- 2007; UA002.002.061.00021 (Box 61)
  - Public Safety Police Dept., 1979 -- 1990; UA002.002.061.00022 (Box 61)
  - Office of Equal Opportunity 2003-, 2003 -- 2007; UA002.002.061.00023 (Box 61)
  - Parking, 1976 -- 2011; UA002.002.061.00024 (Box 61)
  - Facilities and Space, 2002 -- 2005; UA002.002.061.00025 (Box 61)
  - Union- Local 925, 1979 -- 2011; UA002.002.061.00026 (Box 61)
  - Archives, 1998 -- 2010; UA002.002.061.00027 (Box 61)
  - Archivists, 1998 -- 2005; UA002.002.061.00028 (Box 61)
  - Library, 1984 -- 2003; UA002.002.061.00029 (Box 61)
  - Digital Library, 1997 -- 2004; UA002.002.062.00001 (Box 62)
  - University Library Council, 1990 -- 2002; UA002.002.062.00002 (Box 62)
  - University Library Tech Services, 1981 -- 2001; UA002.002.062.00003 (Box 62)
  - Deans and Secondary Deans, 2001; UA002.002.062.00004 (Box 62)
  - FY11 Annual Report, 2011; UA002.002.062.00005 (Box 62)
  - Provost House- 114 South Street, 1990; UA002.002.062.00006 (Box 62)
  - Institutional Research, 1974 -- 2012; UA002.002.062.00007 (Box 62)
  - Risk Register, 2000 -- 2010; UA002.002.062.00008 (Box 62)
  - India Correspondence/Affiliations, 2005 -- 2006; UA002.002.062.00009 (Box 62)
  - Fraud and Research Misconduct Advisory Com. 1996, 1996 -- 2007; UA002.002.062.00010 (Box 62)
  - Research/OVP, 1985 -- 2011; UA002.002.062.00011 (Box 62)
  - Sponsored Research, 1997 -- 2005; UA002.002.062.00012 (Box 62)
  - Study Abroad- General, 1981 -- 1997; UA002.002.062.00013 (Box 62)
  - Undergraduate Experience Task Force, 2003; UA002.002.062.00014 (Box 62)
  - Undergraduate Advising, 1982 -- 2008; UA002.002.062.00015 (Box 62)
  - National Student Loan Clearinghouse, 1996; UA002.002.062.00016 (Box 62)
  - Admissions 2004-, 1998 -- 2004; UA002.002.062.00017 (Box 62)
  - Residences, 1997 -- 2006; UA002.002.062.00018 (Box 62)
  - Health Services, 1985 -- 2009; UA002.002.062.00019 (Box 62)
  - Commencement, 2007; UA002.002.062.00020 (Box 62)
  - Unviersity Council on Graduate Education, 2002 -- 2006; UA002.002.062.00021 (Box 62)
  - Primary Souce, 2007; UA002.002.062.00022 (Box 62)
  - Summer Scholars Program, 1991 -- 1996; UA002.002.062.00023 (Box 62)
  - Organizations on Campus, 1988 -- 1998; UA002.002.062.00024 (Box 62)
  - Drug/Alcohol Abuse, 1987 -- 2011; UA002.002.062.00025 (Box 62)
  - Dining Services, 1988 -- 1991; UA002.002.062.00026 (Box 62)
  - Fraternities/Sororities, 1988 -- 2006; UA002.002.062.00027 (Box 62)
  - Disabilities, 1990 -- 2008; UA002.002.062.00028 (Box 62)
  - Andrew Clark, 2010; UA002.002.062.00029 (Box 62)
  - Boston Higher Education Partnership, 1994 -- 1999; UA002.002.062.00030 (Box 62)
  - Consultants, 1984; UA002.002.062.00031 (Box 62)
  - Africa Forum, 2003; UA002.002.062.00032 (Box 62)
  - Counseling and Mental Health Services, 1973 -- 2004; UA002.002.062.00033 (Box 62)
  - Ballou Hall, 1997; UA002.002.062.00034 (Box 62)
  - Tuition Remission, 1982 -- 1999; UA002.002.062.00035 (Box 62)
  - A Pathway to Success, 2000 -- 2010; UA002.002.063.00001 (Box 63)
  - Audit and Management Advisory Services, 2000 -- 2007; UA002.002.063.00002 (Box 63)
  - University Press of New England, 1978 -- 2006; UA002.002.063.00003 (Box 63)
  - Property, 1985 -- 1999; UA002.002.063.00004 (Box 63)
  - Purchasing Pre 1996, Warranties, Instructions, 1985 -- 1998; UA002.002.063.00005 (Box 63)
  - One Medicine, 1997 -- 2001; UA002.002.063.00006 (Box 63)
  - Nursing Degree, 1983; UA002.002.063.00007 (Box 63)
  - NEH Challenge Grant, 1983 -- 2007; UA002.002.063.00008 (Box 63)
  - TUCC Tufts University Children's Center, 1999 -- 2003; UA002.002.063.00009 (Box 63)
  - Mass Bay Marine Studies Consortium, 1977 -- 2012; UA002.002.063.00010 (Box 63)
  - Foreign Policy Fellows, 2000 -- 2010; UA002.002.063.00011 (Box 63)
  - McCarthy Lectureship, 1998; UA002.002.063.00012 (Box 63)
  - University Relations V.P. for Mary Jeka, 1995 -- 2004; UA002.002.063.00013 (Box 63)
  - Vision Statement, 1996 -- 2001; UA002.002.063.00014 (Box 63)
  - Nutrition School 1991-1996, UA002.002.063.00015 (Box 63)
  - Nutrition School 1997-2001, UA002.002.063.00016 (Box 63)
  - HNRCA, 1998; UA002.002.063.00017 (Box 63)
  - Tufts Centennial, 1997; UA002.002.063.00018 (Box 63)
  - Misc. Tisch College Documents, 2002 -- 2010; UA002.002.063.00019 (Box 63)
  - Financial Aid, Also See Loans, 1986 -- 2003; UA002.002.063.00020 (Box 63)
  - Summer School, 1983 -- 1999; UA002.002.063.00021 (Box 63)
  - ROTC, 1969 -- 2002; UA002.002.063.00022 (Box 63)
  - Research, 2004; UA002.002.063.00023 (Box 63)
  - Hillel, 1985 -- 2002; UA002.002.064.00001 (Box 64)
  - Senior Surveys, 2004 -- 2008; UA002.002.064.00002 (Box 64)
  - Bylaws-Medical 1970-92, 1970 -- 1992; UA002.002.064.00003 (Box 64)
  - Retired and Emiritus 1986-99, 1986 -- 1999; UA002.002.064.00004 (Box 64)
  - Emeriti Lunch/Dinner Social Events, 1997 -- 2009; UA002.002.064.00005 (Box 64)
  - Planning Accredidation Board, 2010; UA002.002.064.00006 (Box 64)
  - One Medicine Initiative Folder 1, 1999 -- 2000; UA002.002.064.00007 (Box 64)
  - One Medicine Initiative Folder 2, 1999 -- 2000; UA002.002.064.00008 (Box 64)
  - Executive Faculty Board Agenda April 6 2000, UA002.002.064.00009 (Box 64)
  - Executive Council Meeting May 1 2000, UA002.002.064.00010 (Box 64)
  - Academic Titles and Meanings Dept of Pathology 1992, UA002.002.064.00011 (Box 64)
  - Tufts Technology, 2011; UA002.002.064.00012 (Box 64)
  - Self Evaluation School of Vetrinary Medicine, 2004; UA002.002.064.00013 (Box 64)
  - AIDS Policy, 1995; UA002.002.064.00014 (Box 64)
  - Affirmative Action/Equal Opportunity Policy, 2002; UA002.002.064.00015 (Box 64)
  - Business Conduct Policy, 1996; UA002.002.064.00016 (Box 64)
  - Faculty Commencement Attendance, 1996; UA002.002.064.00017 (Box 64)
  - Policy on Academic Freedom, Tenure and Retirement, 2001; UA002.002.064.00018 (Box 64)
  - Consensual Relationships Policy, 1991 -- 2007; UA002.002.064.00019 (Box 64)
  - Construction/Renovation Policy, 1980; UA002.002.064.00020 (Box 64)
  - Copyright and Fair Use Policy, 2001 -- 2005; UA002.002.064.00021 (Box 64)
  - Copyright Infringement Policy, 1996; UA002.002.064.00022 (Box 64)
  - Data Security Law Memo, 2010; UA002.002.064.00023 (Box 64)
  - Faculty Death Benefit Policy, 1998; UA002.002.064.00024 (Box 64)
  - Guidelines for Proposing New Degree Programs, 2006; UA002.002.064.00025 (Box 64)
  - Archives Records Authority Statement, 2001; UA002.002.064.00026 (Box 64)
  - Disability Insurance durign Leave w/o Pay, 1982; UA002.002.064.00027 (Box 64)
  - Divestment 1989, UA002.002.064.00028 (Box 64)
  - Drug and Alcohol Abuse Policy, 1993; UA002.002.064.00029 (Box 64)
  - Tufts Email Policy, 2003; UA002.002.064.00030 (Box 64)
  - Emeriti Benefits, 1995; UA002.002.064.00031 (Box 64)
  - Environmental Policy, 1990 -- 2010; UA002.002.064.00032 (Box 64)
  - Equipment Policy, 1997; UA002.002.064.00033 (Box 64)
  - Capital Equipment Policy, 1996; UA002.002.064.00034 (Box 64)
  - FMLA, 1993; UA002.002.064.00035 (Box 64)
  - Statement on Administrative Grade Changes, 2002; UA002.002.064.00036 (Box 64)
  - Sackler Graduate Student Policy, 1993; UA002.002.064.00037 (Box 64)
  - Grant in Aid Policy, 1994; UA002.002.064.00038 (Box 64)
  - Grievance Policy A&S, 1992 -- 1995; UA002.002.064.00039 (Box 64)
  - HNRCA Benefits Policy, 1984; UA002.002.064.00040 (Box 64)
  - Holiday Party Policy, 1996; UA002.002.064.00041 (Box 64)
  - I-9 Policy, 1987; UA002.002.064.00042 (Box 64)
  - Institutional Integrity, 2001; UA002.002.064.00043 (Box 64)
  - Intellectual Property Policy, 1984; UA002.002.064.00044 (Box 64)
  - Tisch Library Circulation Policy, 1997; UA002.002.064.00045 (Box 64)
  - Moving Expense Policy, 1995; UA002.002.064.00046 (Box 64)
  - Nondescrimination Policy, 1985; UA002.002.064.00047 (Box 64)
  - Outside Inquirt Policy, 1989; UA002.002.064.00048 (Box 64)
  - Outside Recruitment Policy, 1984; UA002.002.064.00049 (Box 64)
  - Permanent Residency Scholarship Policy, 1987; UA002.002.064.00050 (Box 64)
  - Vet Starting/Ending On Time Policy, 1997; UA002.002.064.00051 (Box 64)
  - Photo ID Policy Med School, 1995; UA002.002.064.00052 (Box 64)
  - Plagarism Policy, 1990 -- 2010; UA002.002.064.00053 (Box 64)
  - Postering/Chalking Policy, 1996; UA002.002.064.00054 (Box 64)
  - Access to Student Information Policy, 1994; UA002.002.064.00055 (Box 64)
  - Political Activities, 1996 -- 2004; UA002.002.064.00056 (Box 64)
  - Scientific Misconduct Policy, 1992; UA002.002.064.00057 (Box 64)
  - Sexual Harassment Policy, 1998; UA002.002.064.00058 (Box 64)
  - Smoking in the Workplace, 1992; UA002.002.064.00059 (Box 64)
  - Supplemental Pay Policy, 1995; UA002.002.064.00060 (Box 64)
  - Survey Policy, 1996; UA002.002.064.00061 (Box 64)
  - Telephone Fraud Policy, 1996; UA002.002.064.00062 (Box 64)
  - AS&E Tenure Clock Policy, 2003; UA002.002.064.00063 (Box 64)
  - Business Expense Policy, 1993 -- 2002; UA002.002.064.00064 (Box 64)
  - Use of Tufts Name and Insignias Policy, 2001; UA002.002.064.00065 (Box 64)
  - Vacation Policy, 2010; UA002.002.064.00066 (Box 64)
  - Inclement Weather Policy, 1994; UA002.002.064.00067 (Box 64)
  - Tenure and Promotion Committee A&S, 1962 -- 1999; UA002.002.065.00001 (Box 65)
  - General Counsel, 1984 -- 1995; UA002.002.065.00002 (Box 65)
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - Centers/Institutes, 1975 -- 2006; UA002.002.065.00003 (Box 65)
  - Centers- General, 2010; UA002.002.065.00004 (Box 65)
  - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1971 -- 2006; UA002.002.065.00005 (Box 65)
  - American Council on Ed ACE, 1983 -- 2005; UA002.002.065.00006 (Box 65)
  - Association of American Colleges and Universities, 1970 -- 1994; UA002.002.065.00007 (Box 65)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 2006; UA002.002.065.00008 (Box 65)
  - Accrediting Engineering, 1994; UA002.002.065.00009 (Box 65)
  - 2003 Accredidation, UA002.002.065.00010 (Box 65)
  - Associations General, 1986 -- 2006; UA002.002.065.00011 (Box 65)
  - Africana Center, 1982 -- 1989; UA002.002.065.00012 (Box 65)
  - Center for Animals and Public Policy, 1988; UA002.002.065.00013 (Box 65)
  - Asian Center, 1987; UA002.002.065.00014 (Box 65)
  - Center for Engineering Education and Outreach, 2010; UA002.002.065.00015 (Box 65)
  - Center for Enhancement of Learning and Teaching CELT, 2006; UA002.002.065.00016 (Box 65)
  - CENTA, 1992 -- 1999; UA002.002.065.00017 (Box 65)
  - Cosmology Center, 1988; UA002.002.065.00018 (Box 65)
  - Center for the Study of Drug Development, 2002; UA002.002.065.00019 (Box 65)
  - Wright Center Annual Reports, 1992 -- 2004; UA002.002.065.00020 (Box 65)
  - International Center, 1984 -- 1993; UA002.002.065.00021 (Box 65)
  - Center fo South Asian and Indian Ocean Studies, 1994; UA002.002.065.00022 (Box 65)
  - Institute for Foreign Policy Analysis, 1976 -- 2012; UA002.002.065.00023 (Box 65)
  - Tufts Institute of the Environment, 1999 -- 2003; UA002.002.065.00024 (Box 65)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges - Conferences, 2003; UA002.002.066.00001 (Box 66)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges - Conferences, 2004; UA002.002.066.00002 (Box 66)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges - Conferences, 2005; UA002.002.066.00003 (Box 66)
  - Medical School Graduation Questionnaire, 2005; UA002.002.066.00004 (Box 66)
  - Meetings, 2002 -- 2005; UA002.002.066.00005 (Box 66)
  - Organizational Studies, 2002; UA002.002.066.00006 (Box 66)
  - Policy Guidance on Graduate Medical Education, 2001; UA002.002.066.00007 (Box 66)